Papers of the International Labor Defense on Microfilm 5815 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 0913. Box 2/Folder c5. Scottsboro case. Alabama v. Patterson. Circuit Court of Morgan County, Alabama. Deposition of David Schriftman. 5 pages., 1933; 30 (Reel 2)
- 0918. Box 2/Folder c5. Scottsboro case. Alabama v. Patterson. Circuit Court of Morgan County, Alabama. Deposition of Jim Jones. 6 pages., 1933; 31 (Reel 2)
- 0924. Box 2/Folder c6. Scottsboro case. Alabama v. Kone, Swift, and Pearson. 39 pages., 1934; 32 (Reel 2)
  October 1934.
- 0925. Box 2/Folder c6. Scottsboro case. Alabama v. Kone, Swift, and Pearson. Inferior Court of Huntsville, Alabama. Transcript. 38 pages., 1934; 33 (Reel 2)
- 0001. Box 2/Folder c7. Scottsboro case. Eugene Williams/Roy Wright Cases. 44 pages., 1932-1933; 1 (Reel 3)
  June 1932-May 1933.
- 0030. Box 2/Folder c7. Scottsboro case. Alabama v. Wright and Williams. Circuit Court of Jackson County, Alabama. Statement of Facts and Petition for a Writ of Habeas Corpus. 13 pages., 1933; 2 (Reel 3)
  April 28-May 4, 1933.
- 0045. Box 2/Folder c8. Scottsboro case. Haywood Patterson/Clarence Norris Cases. 135 pages., 1933-1934; 3 (Reel 3)
  May 1933-February 1934
- 0046. Box 2/Folder c8. Scottsboro case. Alabama v. Patterson. Circuit Court of Morgan County, Alabama. Brief on Motion for a New Trial. 38 pages., 4 (Reel 3)
- 0084. Box 2/Folder c8. Scottsboro case. Affidavit of Charles H. Houston and Edward P. Lovett on Exclusion of Negroes from Jury Service in Loudon County, Virginia. 5 pages., 1933; 5 (Reel 3)
  March 10, 1933
- 0089. Box 2/Folder c8. Scottsboro case. Letter to Attorney General Knight and Judge Callahan of Decatur, Alabama, from Ruby Bates regarding the Innocence of the Scottsboro Boys. 1 page., 1933; 6 (Reel 3)
  November 29, 1933
- 0090. Box 2/Folder c8. Scottsboro case. Alabama v. Patterson Circuit Court of Morgan County, Alabama. Order and Judgment for New Trial Granted by Judge James E. Horton. 24 pages., 1933; 7 (Reel 3)
  June 22, 1933.
- 0114. Box 2/Folder c8. Scottsboro case. Alabama v. Norris. Circuit Court of Morgan County, Alabama. Brief for Defendant on Motion for New Trial. 48 pages., 8 (Reel 3)
- 0162. Box 2/Folder c8. Scottsboro case. Alabama v. Patterson and Alabama v. Norris. Circuit Court of Morgan County, Alabama. Brief for Defendants on Constitutional Questions. 28 pages., 1934; 9 (Reel 3)
  February 5, 1934
- 0190. Box 2/Folder c9. Scottsboro case. Haywood Patterson Case (United States Supreme Court Decision). 7 pages., 1935; 10 (Reel 3)
  April 1935
- 0191. Box 2/Folder c9. Scottsboro case. Patterson v. Alabama. United States Supreme Court. Opinion by Chief Justice Charles Evans Hughes. 6 pages., 1935; 11 (Reel 3)
  April 1935.
- 0197. Box 2/Folder c10. Scottsboro case. Legal Correspondence. 45 pages., 1934; 12 (Reel 3)
  October-November 1934.
- 0242. Box 2/Folder c11. Scottsboro case. Haywood Patterson Case. 15 pages., 1935-1936; 13 (Reel 3)
  December 1935-January 1936
- 0257. Box 2/Folder c12. Scottsboro case. Joseph Brodsky. 29 pages., 1934-1935; 14 (Reel 3)
- 0271. Box 2/Folder c12. Scottsboro case. Statement of Joseph Brodsky regarding Conflicts with Samuel Leibowitz ad George Chamlee and the Defense of the Scottsboro Boys. 15 pages., 1934; 15 (Reel 3)
  October 30, 1934
- 0286. Box 3/Folder c13. Scottsboro case. Publicity and Organization: General. 32 pages., 1931; 16 (Reel 3)
- 0318. Box 3/Folder c14. Scottsboro case. Publicity and Organization: General. 92 pages., 1932; 17 (Reel 3)
- 0381. Box 3/Folder c14. Scottsboro case. "The Supreme Court vs. Civil Liberty: Dissenting Opinions of Justices Brandeis and Holmes in Cases Affecting Civil Liberty," by the American Civil Liberties Union. 9 pages., 1927; 18 (Reel 3)
  October 1927.
- 0390. Box 3/Folder c14. Scottsboro case. "Alabama Town: The Story of the 9 Scottsboro Boys," by Lowell Wakefield, National Youth Committee of the International Labor Defense. 11 pages., 1932; 19 (Reel 3)
- 0410. Box 3/Folder c15. Scottsboro case. Leaflets, Postcards, and Contribution Books. 126 pages., 1933; 20 (Reel 3)
  January-June 1933.
- 0526. Box 3/Folder c16. Scottsboro case. Publicity and Organization: General. 41 pages., 1933; 21 (Reel 3)
  July-December 1933.
- 0567. Box 3/Folder c17. Scottsboro case. Publicity and Organization: General. 161 pages., 1934; 22 (Reel 3)
- 0631. Box 3/Folder c17. Scottsboro case. "Mr. President: Free the Scottsboro Boys," by International Labor Defense. 17 pages., 1934; 23 (Reel 3)
  August 1934
- 0728. Box 3/Folder c18. Scottsboro case. Publicity and Organization: General. 35 pages., 1935; 24 (Reel 3)
- 0763. Box 3/Folder c19. Scottsboro case. Publicity and Organization: General. 44 pages., 1936; 25 (Reel 3)
- 0817. Box 3/Folder c20. Scottsboro case. Publicity and Organization: General. 63 pages., 1937-1941; 26 (Reel 3)
- 0879. Box 3/Folder c21. Scottsboro case. Ada Wright/J. Louis Engdahl. 11 pages., 1932; 27 (Reel 3)
- 0890. Box 3/Folder c22. Scottsboro case. Lowell Wakefield. 9 pages., 1932; 28 (Reel 3)
  March 1932
- 0899. Box 3/Folder c23. Scottsboro case. Ruby Bates, Janie Patterson, Richard B. Moore, Lester Carter, et al. 35 pages., 1933; 29 (Reel 3)
  May-June 1933
- 0934. Box 3/Folder c24. Scottsboro case. Angelo Herndon, Ida Norris, and Richard B. Moor. 9 pages., 1934; 30 (Reel 3)
  September-October 1934.
- 0943. Box 3/Folder c25. Scottsboro case. Roy Wright, Olen Montgomery, and Richard B. Moore. 12 pages., 1937; 31 (Reel 3)
- 0955. Box 3/Folder c26. Scottsboro case. National Committee for the Defense of Political Prisoners. 70 pages., 1932-1934; 32 (Reel 3)
- 0981. Box 3/Folder c26. Scottsboro case. "Eight Who Lie in the Death House," by Paul Peters, National Committee for the Defense of Political Prisoners. 7 pages., 1932; 33 (Reel 3)
- 0001. Box 3/Folder c27. Scottsboro case. Scottsboro Unity Defense Committee. 38 pages., 1932-1933; 1 (Reel 4)
- 0039. Box 3/Folder c28. Scottsboro case. Scottsboro Defense Committee. 25 pages., 1935-1936; 2 (Reel 4)
- 0064. Box 3/Folder c29. Scottsboro case. Scottsboro Defense Committee. 66 pages., 1935-1936; 3 (Reel 4)
- 0130. Box 3/Folder c30. Scottsboro case. Scottsboro Defense Committee. 18 pages., 1937; 4 (Reel 4)
- 0148. Box 3/Folder c31. Scottsboro case. Scottsboro Defense Committee. 26 pages., 1938; 5 (Reel 4)
- 0174. Box 3/Folder c32. Scottsboro case. Scottsboro Defense Committee. 39 pages., 1939-1940; 6 (Reel 4)
- 0213. Box 4/Folder c33. Scottsboro case. Important Documents - Affidavits, Letters, Receipts, Photostats. 63 pages., 1931-1934; 7 (Reel 4)
- 0214. Box 4/Folder c33. Scottsboro case. Affidavit of Ruby Bates regarding Innocence of Eugene Williams. 1 page., 1931; 8 (Reel 4)
  March 25, 1931
- 0216. Box 4/Folder c33. Scottsboro case. Letter to Earl Streetman from Ruby Bates Recanting Accusations. 3 pages., 1932; 9 (Reel 4)
  January 5, 1932.
- 0219. Box 4/Folder c33. Scottsboro case. Statement by the Scottsboro Boys regarding the International Labor Defense. 1 page., 10 (Reel 4)
- 0220. Box 4/Folder c33. Scottsboro case. Report on Interview with Scottsboro Boys in Birmingham, Alabama, by Benjamin J. Davis. 5 pages., 1933; 11 (Reel 4)
  May 13, 1933
- 0225. Box 4/Folder c33. Scottsboro case. Statement by the Scottsboro Boys Affirming and Ratifying the Retainer by the International Labor Defense of George W. Chamlee. 1 page, 1931; 12 (Reel 4)
  April 20, 1931
- 0231. Box 4/Folder c33. Scottsboro case. Facts in the Scottsboro Cases and the Controversy with the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People as Investigated by George W. Chamlee. 7 pages., 13 (Reel 4)
- 0240. Box 4/Folder c33. Scottsboro case. The Scottsboro Boys, by Ben Davis. 23 pages., 1934; 14 (Reel 4)
  April 1934.
- 0263. Box 4/Folder c33. Scottsboro case. Affidavit of Ruby Bates regarding Innocence of Eugene Williams. 1 page., 1933; 15 (Reel 4)
  May 17, 1933
- 0275. Box 4/Folder c33. Scottsboro case. Affidavit of Lester Carter regarding Personal Character of Attorney Stephen R. Roddy. 1 page., 1931; 16 (Reel 4)
  October 27, 1931
- 0276. Box 4/Folder c34. Scottsboro case. Telegrams and Resolutions to Governor Benjamin M. Miller, et al. 78 pages., 1931; 17 (Reel 4)
- 0354. Box 4/Folder c35. Scottsboro case. Lawyers' Statements after First United States Supreme Court Decision. 6 pages., 1932; 18 (Reel 4)
  November 1932
- 0360. Box 4/Folder c36. Scottsboro case. Ruby Bates' Letter to Earl Streetman. 39 pages., 1933; 19 (Reel 4)
  January-March 1933
- 0399. Box 4/Folder c37. Scottsboro case. Decatur, Alabama Lynchings. 47 pages., 1933; 20 (Reel 4)
  August-October 1933
- 0446. Box 4/Folder c38. Scottsboro case. Visit of Scottsboro Mothers to Washington, D.C. 81 pages., 1934; 21 (Reel 4)
  April-May 1934
- 0527. Box 4/Folder c39. Scottsboro case. American Scottsboro Committee. 8 pages., 1934; 22 (Reel 4)
  October-November 1934
- 0535. Box 4/Folder c40. Scottsboro case. Visit of Scottsboro Mothers to Birmingham, Alabama. 32 pages., 1934; 23 (Reel 4)
  November-December 1934
- 0567. Box 4/Folder c41. Scottsboro case. Negro Jurors Ruling by United States Supreme Court. 59 pages., 1935; 24 (Reel 4)
- 0626. Box 4/Folder c42. Scottsboro case. Chain Gang Burning in Scottsboro, Alabama. 34 pages., 1936; 25 (Reel 4)
  January-February 1936
- 0660. Box 4/Folder c43. Scottsboro case. General Correspondence (includes William M. Trotter's letter for National Association for the Advancement of Colored People to International Labor Defense). 42 pages., 1931; 26 (Reel 4)
- 0702. Box 4/Folder c44. Scottsboro case. General Correspondence (includes congratulations after first United States Supreme Court Decision). 26 pages., 1932; 27 (Reel 4)
- 0728. Box 4/Folder c45. Scottsboro case. General Correspondence (includes "crank letters"). 73 pages., 1933; 28 (Reel 4)
  January-May 1933
- 0801. Box 4/Folder c46. Scottsboro case. General Correspondence (includes "crank letters"). 47 pages., 1933; 29 (Reel 4)
  June-December 1933.
- 0848. Box 4/Folder c47. Scottsboro case. General Correspondence. 55 pages., 1934; 30 (Reel 4)
- 0903. Box 4/Folder c48. Scottsboro case. General Correspondence. 24 pages., 1935; 31 (Reel 4)
- 0927. Box 4/Folder c49. Scottsboro case. General Correspondence. 9 pages., 1936-1937; 32 (Reel 4)
- 0936. Box 4/Folder c50. Scottsboro case. General Correspondence. 44 pages., 1938; 33 (Reel 4)
- 0001. Box 4/Folder c51. Scottsboro case. General Correspondence. 9 pages., 1939; 1 (Reel 5)
- 0010. Box 4/Folder c52. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Montgomery, Olen. 62 pages., 1932-1938; 2 (Reel 5)
- 0072. Box 4/Folder c53. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Norris, Clarence. 136 pages., 1932-1944; 3 (Reel 5)
- 0208. Box 5/Folder c54. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Patterson, Haywood. 77 pages., 1931-1936; 4 (Reel 5)
- 0285. Box 5/Folder c55. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Patterson, Haywood. 129 pages., 1937-1940; 5 (Reel 5)
- 0414. Box 5/Folder c56. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Patterson, Haywood. 66 pages., 1941-1943; 6 (Reel 5)
- 0480. Box 5/Folder c57. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Patterson, Haywood. 107 pages., 1944-1946; 7 (Reel 5)
- 0587. Box 5/Folder c58. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Powell, Ozie. 54 pages., 1932-1944; 8 (Reel 5)
- 0641. Box 5/Folder c59. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Roberson, Willie. 47 pages., 1934-1942; 9 (Reel 5)
- 0688. Box 5/Folder c60. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Weems, Charley. 99 pages., 1932-1944; 10 (Reel 5)
- 0787. Box 5/Folder c61. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Williams, Eugene. 21 pages., 1932-1937; 11 (Reel 5)
- 0808. Box 5/Folder c62. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Wright, Andy. 65 pages., 1932-1940; 12 (Reel 5)
- 0873. Box 5/Folder c63. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Wright, Andy. 87 pages., 1941-1945; 13 (Reel 5)
- 0960. Box 5/Folder c64. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Wright, Roy. 17 pages., 1931-1937; 14 (Reel 5)
- 0977. Box 5/Folder c65. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Montgomery Family. 58 pages., 1932-1943; 15 (Reel 5)
- 0001. Box 5/Folder c66. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Norris Family. 89 pages., 1934-1944; 1 (Reel 6)
- 0090. Box 5/Folder c67. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Patterson Family. 97 pages., 1934-1945; 2 (Reel 6)
- 0187. Box 5/Folder c68. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Powell Family. 89 pages., 1934-1944; 3 (Reel 6)
- 0276. Box 5/Folder c69. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Roberson Family. 5 pages., 1937-1940; 4 (Reel 6)
- 0281. Box 5/Folder c70. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Weems Family. 6 pages., 1932-1939; 5 (Reel 6)
- 0287. Box 5/Folder c71. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Williams Family. 16 pages., 1934-1940; 6 (Reel 6)
- 0303. Box 5/Folder c72. Scottsboro case. Correspondence: Wright Family. 28 pages., 1934-1944; 7 (Reel 6)
- 0331. Box 6/Folder c73. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous Newsclippings.11 pages., 1931; 8 (Reel 6)
  March 1931
- 0342. Box 6/Folder c74. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous Newsclippings.67 pages., 1931; 9 (Reel 6)
  April 1-15, 1931
- 0409. Box 6/Folder c75. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings. 47 pages., 1931; 10 (Reel 6)
  April 16-30, 1931 (1)
- 0456. Box 6/Folder c76. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.39 pages., 1931; 11 (Reel 6)
  April 16-30, 1931 (2)
- 0495. Box 6/Folder c77. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings. 36 pages., 1931; 12 (Reel 6)
  May 1931 (1)
- 0531. Box 6/Folder c78. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.60 pages., 1931; 13 (Reel 6)
  May 1931 (2)
- 0591. Box 6/Folder c79. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.46 pages., 1931; 14 (Reel 6)
  May 1931 (3)
- 0637. Box 6/Folder c80. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings. 49 pages., 1931; 15 (Reel 6)
  May 1931 (4)
- 0686. Box 6/Folder c81. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.37 pages., 1931; 16 (Reel 6)
  May 1931 (5)
- 0723. Box 6/Folder c82. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.21 pages., 1931; 17 (Reel 6)
  June 1931 (1)
- 0744. Box 6/Folder c83. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.30 pages., 1931; 18 (Reel 6)
  June 1931 (2)
- 0774. Box 6/Folder c84. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.48 pages., 1931; 19 (Reel 6)
  June 1931 (3)
- 0822. Box 6/Folder c85. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings. 33 pages., 1931; 20 (Reel 6)
  June 1931 (4)
- 0855. Box 6/Folder c86. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings. 35 pages., 1931; 21 (Reel 6)
  June 1931 (5)
- 0890. Box 7/Folder c87. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.49 pages., 1931; 22 (Reel 6)
  July 1931 (1)
- 0939. Box 7/Folder c88. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.36 pages., 1931; 23 (Reel 6)
  July 1931 (2)
- 0975. Box 7/Folder c89. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.39 pages., 1931; 24 (Reel 6)
  July 1931 (3)
- 0001. Box 7/Folder c90. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.50 pages., 1931; 1 (Reel 7)
  August-October 1931 (1)
- 0051. Box 7/Folder c91. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.40 pages., 1931; 2 (Reel 7)
  August-October 1931 (2)
- 0091. Box 7/Folder c92. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.98 pages., 1931-1932; 3 (Reel 7)
  November 1931-January 1932 (1)
- 0189. Box 7/Folder c93. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings. 99 pages., 1931-1932; 4 (Reel 7)
  November 1931-January 1932 (2)
- 0288. Box 7/Folder c94. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings (Lowell Wakefield Tour).70 pages., 1932; 5 (Reel 7)
  February-April 1932.
- 0358. Box 7/Folder c95. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings (Lowell Wakefield Tour). 59 pages., 1932; 6 (Reel 7)
  February-April 1932
- 0417. Box 7/Folder c96. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings (Ada Wright/J. Louis Engdahl tour). 26 pages., 1932; 7 (Reel 7)
  May-August 1932
- 0443. Box 7/Folder c97. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.53 pages., 1932; 8 (Reel 7)
  September-October 1932
- 0496. Box 7/Folder c98. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.45 pages., 1932; 9 (Reel 7)
- 0541. Box 7/Folder c99. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.68 pages., 1932-1933; 10 (Reel 7)
  December 1932-February 1933
- 0609. Box 7/Folder c100. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings. 31 pages., 1933; 11 (Reel 7)
  March 1933
- 0640. Box 7/Folder c101. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.45 pages., 1933; 12 (Reel 7)
  April 1933
- 0685. Box 7/Folder c102. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.28 pages., 1933; 13 (Reel 7)
- 0713. Box 7/Folder c103. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.11 pages., 1933; 14 (Reel 7)
  June 1933
- 0724. Box 7/Folder c104. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.18 pages., 1933; 15 (Reel 7)
  July 1933
- 0742. Box 7/Folder c105. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.36 pages., 1933; 16 (Reel 7)
- 0778. Box 7/Folder c106. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.42 pages., 1933; 17 (Reel 7)
  September-December 1933
- 0820. Box 7/Folder c107. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.64 pages., 1934; 18 (Reel 7)
  January 1934
- 0884. Box 7/Folder c108. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.40 pages., 1934; 19 (Reel 7)
  February 1934
- 0924. Box 7/Folder c109. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.44 pages., 1934; 20 (Reel 7)
  March 1934.
- 0968. Box 7/Folder c110. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.29 pages., 1934; 21 (Reel 7)
  April 1934
- 0001. Box 8/Folder c111. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.41 pages., 1934; 1 (Reel 8)
  May 1934
- 0042. Box 8/Folder c112. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.29 pages., 1934; 2 (Reel 8)
  June 1934
- 0071. Box 8/Folder c113. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.25 pages., 1934; 3 (Reel 8)
- 0096. Box 8/Folder c114. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.37 pages., 1934; 4 (Reel 8)
- 0133. Box 8/Folder c115. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.9 pages., 1934; 5 (Reel 8)
  September 1934
- 0142. Box 8/Folder c116. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.76 pages., 1934; 6 (Reel 8)
  October 1934 (1)
- 0218. Box 8/Folder c117. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.64 pages., 1934; 7 (Reel 8)
  October 1934 (2)
- 0282. Box 8/Folder c118. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.67 pages., 1934; 8 (Reel 8)
  October 1934 (3)
- 0349. Box 8/Folder c119. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.67 pages., 1834; 9 (Reel 8)
  November 1834
- 0416. Box 8/Folder c120. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.37 pages., 1934; 10 (Reel 8)
  December 1934
- 0453. Box 8/Folder c121. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.39 pages., 1935; 11 (Reel 8)
  January 1935
- 0492. Box 8/Folder c122. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.51 pages., 1935; 12 (Reel 8)
  February-March 1935
- 0543. Box 8/Folder c123. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.84 pages., 1935; 13 (Reel 8)
  April 1935 (1)
- 0627. Box 8/Folder c124. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.42 pages., 1935; 14 (Reel 8)
  April 1935 (2)
- 0669. Box 8/Folder c125. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.67 pages., 1935; 15 (Reel 8)
  April 1935 (3)
- 0736. Box 8/Folder c126. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.40 pages., 1935; 16 (Reel 8)
  May 1935
- 0776. Box 8/Folder c127. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.15 pages., 1935; 17 (Reel 8)
  June 1935
- 0791. Box 8/Folder c128. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.32 pages., 1935; 18 (Reel 8)
  July 1935
- 0823. Box 8/Folder c129. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.13 pages., 1935; 19 (Reel 8)
  August 1935
- 0836. Box 8/Folder c130. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.17 pages., 1935; 20 (Reel 8)
  September 1935
- 0853. Box 8/Folder c131. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.20 pages., 1935; 21 (Reel 8)
  October-December 1935
- 0873. Box 8/Folder 132. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.18 pages., 1936; 22 (Reel 8)
  January-March 1936.
- 0891. Box 8/Folder 133. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.13 pages., 1936; 23 (Reel 8)
  April-May 1936
- 0904. Box 8/Folder c134. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.24 pages., 1936; 24 (Reel 8)
  June-September 1936
- 0928. Box 8/Folder c135. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.16 pages., 1936; 25 (Reel 8)
  October[-December] 1936.
- 0944. Box 8/Folder c136. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.8 pages., 1937; 26 (Reel 8)
  January-March 1937
- 0952. Box 8/Folder c137. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.6 pages., 1937; 27 (Reel 8)
  April 1937
- 0958. Box 8/Folder c138. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.21 pages., 1937; 28 (Reel 8)
  May 1937
- 0001. Box 8/Folder c139. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.13 pages., 1937; 1 (Reel 9)
  June 1937
- 0014. Box 8/Folder c140. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.16 pages., 1937; 2 (Reel 9)
  July-September 1937
- 0030. Box 8/Folder c141. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.14 pages., 1937; 3 (Reel 9)
  October[-December] 1937 (1)
- 0054. Box 8/Folder c142. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.24 pages., 1937; 4 (Reel 9)
  October 1937 (2)
- 0078. Box 8/Folder c143. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.3 pages., 1938; 5 (Reel 9)
  January-February 1938
- 0081. Box 9/Folder c144. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.26 pages., 1938; 6 (Reel 9)
  March 1938
- 0107. Box 9/Folder c145. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.17 pages., 1938; 7 (Reel 9)
  April-May 1938
- 0124. Box 9/Folder c146. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.25 pages., 1938; 8 (Reel 9)
  June 1938
- 0149. Box 9/Folder c147. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings. 30 pages., 1938; 9 (Reel 9)
  July 1938
- 0179. Box 9/Folder c148. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.12 pages., 1938; 10 (Reel 9)
  August 1938
- 0191. Box 9/Folder c149. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.26 pages., 1938; 11 (Reel 9)
  September[-November] 1938.
- 0217. Box 9/Folder c150. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.10 pages., 1938; 12 (Reel 9)
  December 1938
- 0227. Box 9/Folder c151. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.35 pages., 1939; 13 (Reel 9)
- 0262. Box 9/Folder c152. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.16 pages., 1940; 14 (Reel 9)
- 0278. Box 9/Folder c153. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings. 6 pages., 1941; 15 (Reel 9)
- 0284. Box 9/Folder c154. Scottsboro case. Miscellaneous News clippings.9 pages., 1942; 16 (Reel 9)
- 0293. Box 9/Folder c155. Scottsboro case. Editorial. 26 pages., 1931; 17 (Reel 9)
  April 1931
- 0319. Box 9/Folder c156. Scottsboro case. Editorial. 47 pages., 1931; 18 (Reel 9)
  May 1931.
- 0366. Box 9/Folder c157. Scottsboro case. Editorial. 28 pages., 1931; 19 (Reel 9)
- 0394. Box 9/Folder c158. Scottsboro case. Editorial. 21 pages., 1931; 20 (Reel 9)
- 0415. Box 9/Folder c159. Scottsboro case. Editorial. 32 pages., 1931; 21 (Reel 9)
- 0447. Box 9/Folder c160. Scottsboro case. Editorial. 23 pages., 1931; 22 (Reel 9)
- 0470. Box 9/Folder c161. Scottsboro case. Editorial. 16 pages., 1931; 23 (Reel 9)
  August-October 1931.
- 0486. Box 9/Folder c162. Scottsboro case. Editorial. 33 pages., 1932; 24 (Reel 9)
- 0519. Box 9/Folder c163. Scottsboro case. Editorial. 16 pages., 1932-1933; 25 (Reel 9)
- 0535. Box 9/Folder c164. Scottsboro case. Editorial. 15 pages., 1933; 26 (Reel 9)
  March-July 1933
- 0550. Box 9/Folder c165. Scottsboro case. Appeals for Funds. 38 pages., 1933; 27 (Reel 9)
  March-May 1933
- 0588. Box 10/Folder c166. Scottsboro case. Press Release. 7 pages., 1931; 28 (Reel 9)
  June 1931
- 0595. Box 10/Folder c167. Scottsboro case. Press Release. 53 pages., 1932; 29 (Reel 9)
- 0648. Box 10/Folder c168. Scottsboro case. Press Release. 13 pages., 1933; 30 (Reel 9)
  January-February 1933
- 0661. Box 10/Folder c169. Scottsboro case. Press Release. 108 pages., 1933; 31 (Reel 9)
- 0769. Box 10/Folder c170. Scottsboro case. Press Release. 114 pages., 1933; 32 (Reel 9)